谁想出要餐馆的人都穿上溜冰鞋的点子
So whose idea was it to put everybody in the diner on skates?
某个白痴客人投书意见箱
Some idiot customer put a suggestion in the suggestion box.
- 天啊 他们接受我的建议   - 是你干的
- Oh, my God. They took my idea.     - That was you?
对
Yeah.
好了 来吧
Okay, there you go.
瑞秋 我帮你泡了一杯可可亚
Rachel, I made you a cocoa.
那真的是…
Oh, that's so... Aah!
- 天啊 你们没事吧   - 你没事吧
- Oh, my God. Are you guys okay?     - You all right?
天啊
Oh, my.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 纵有狂风暴雨 #
# When the rain starts to pour #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 支持一如往昔 #
# Like I've been there before #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
留起山羊胡 你看起来蛮像撒旦的
You know, with that goatee, you kind of look like Satan.
所以神父朝我洒圣水
Oh, so that's why the priest threw holy water on me.
听着 你得打起精神
Okay, listen, you have to cheer up.
好吗 你该跟我及罗斯一起出去玩
Okay? You should come out with Ross and me.
那总比整天坐在这里为了凯特哭泣还好
I mean, anything is better than sitting around here crying all day about Kate.
我会哭是因为…
Hey, I was crying because...
因为没有人相信昆西的理论 好吗
Because nobody believed Quincy's theory, okay?
我要上电视了
Hey. I'm gonna be on TV.
- 不可能   - 对
- No way.     - Yeah.
他们要找专家讨论在秘鲁发现的化石
They're putting together this panel to talk about these fossils they found in Peru.
探索频道要来录影
The Discovery Channel's gonna film it.
天啊 谁会看那种节目
Oh, my God. Heh. Who's gonna watch that?
- 谢了 可以出门了吗   - 当然
- Thanks. You ready to go?     - Yeah.
我看过一个女孩穿那件背心
Ahem, I saw a girl with that vest.
谢了
Thanks.
多数人觉得巧克力兔子跟篮子是传统复活节礼物
- Most of us think of chocolate bunnies and baskets as traditional Easter gifts.
有些人坚持送活的小鸡当礼物
Some people insist on giving live chicks as presents.
不幸地是事实上
Unfortunately, the sad fact remains...
这些小家伙活不过国庆日
...that most of these little guys won't live to see the Fourth of July.
因为照顾不周 他们都会死掉
Because as a result of improper care, they will be dead.
你们有卖小鸡
You guys got any of those baby chicks?
我看到电视广告
Because I was watching this, uh, commercial on TV...
天啊 那些小鸡好可爱
...and, man, those things are cute.
（月光餐馆）
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
彼特 你回来了 快来看看这个
Oh, Pete, you're back. Hey, check this out.
哇 溜冰鞋
Wow. Skates. Ha, ha.
你比钱德壮多了 他真的是跟纸片人差不多
Wow. You're a lot sturdier than Chandler. He crumbled like a piece of paper.
你一路还顺风吗
So how was your trip?
- 还可以   - 你帮我带了什么
- Well...     - Oh, what did you bring me?
日本饭店的沐浴用品
Aw, hotel toiletries from Japan. Oh.
我会把它们列为永久收藏品
These are gonna go in my permanent collection.
- 你要喝咖啡吗   - 当然要
- You want some coffee?     - Sure, that'd be great.
好吧
Okay.
一般或无咖啡因
Regular or decaf?
- 最近的就可以了   - 好的
- Uh, whichever's closest.     - All right.
- 好吧   - 问我今天做了什么
- Okay.     - So ask me what I did today.
今天你做了什么
So, what did you do today, Pete?
我买了一家餐厅 想雇用你当主厨
I bought a restaurant, and I would like you to be the chef.
什么
What? Oh.
你能相信他为我买了一家餐厅吗
Can you believe he just offered me a restaurant?
真是个混蛋 你要我踢他屁股吗
What a jerk. You want me to kick his ass?
这一直是我的梦想 自从我买了第一个快速烤箱
I mean, this has been my dream since I got my first Easy-Bake Oven...
开了第一家快速摩妮卡面包店后
...and opened Easy-Monica's Bakery.
我是说我能胜任这份工作 这份工作难不了我
I mean, I would kill for this job. I mean, I can totally do this job...
天知道我已经受够了
...and God knows I've paid my dues. Ugh.
但彼特会这么做是因为他喜欢我
But Pete's just doing this because he has a crush on me.
- 你还是对他没感觉   - 没错
- And you're still not attracted to him at all?     - Mm. No.
我怎么能接受他送我餐厅 我没办法
I mean, how could I accept a restaurant from him? I can't.
我念七年级时 就没办法收下史都文森送我的项链
I couldn't even accept a necklace from Stu Vincent in the seventh grade.
摩妮卡 那不一样 他是你的健康教育老师
Yeah, Mon, that was totally different. He was your health teacher.
怎么了甜心
What, honey?
自从昨天你撞到我后 我的肋骨一直痛到现在
Ow, my side still hurts from when you crashed into me yesterday.
- 天啊 我好抱歉   - 我知道
- Oh, God, I'm so sorry.     - I know. Ow.
天啊
Oh, God.
美女们 猜猜怎么了
Hey, you guys. Guess what.
你要到观光游轮工作
Got a job on a riverboat?
你知道吗 因为你很讨厌它 所以我一年没穿这套西装
You know what? I didn't wear this suit for a year because you hated it.
你猜怎么了 你不再是我的女朋友了
Guess what. You're not my girlfriend anymore, so...
我懂了 你用这套西装发表宣言
Oh, I see. So this suit is making a point.
现在你是单身 你有耍呆的自由
Now that you're on your own, you're free to look as stupid as you'd like.
你很喜欢 对吧
You like it, right?
当然 我觉得你穿上它比肯德基爷爷帅多了
Absolutely. I like it even more on you than I did on Colonel Sanders.
罗斯 我是开玩笑的 快回来
Huh. Ross, Ross, I'm kidding. Come here.
- 你要跟我们说什么   - 你怎么发明轧棉机的
- What were you gonna tell us?     - Was it how you invented the cotton gin?
好吧 再见
Okay, goodbye.
你投书意见箱后
So, um, after you put the suggestion in the box...
餐馆多久后要大家穿上溜冰鞋
...how long did it take for the roller-skating thing to happen?
大约三个月
Um, about three months.
好吧 我想再过两星期
Okay, so I guess that's about, uh, two weeks...
就可以看到上空服务生了
...before the topless thing kicks in.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
我买了一样东西要送你 快打开
I got you something. Open it. Open it.
好吧
Okay.
是一只鸡
It's a chicken.
很可爱吧
It's cute, huh?
你们了解鸡吗
Whoa, whoa, whoa. You guys, do you know anything about chicks?
了解鸡 不
Fowl? No.
了解女人 不
Women? No.
好吧 这是一份重责大任
Okay, well, they are a huge responsibility.
特别是在这个年龄 他们随时都需要照顾
Especially at this age. They require constant care.
他们需要正确的食物 还有许多的爱
They need just the right food and lots and lots of love.
没问题
Oh, well, no problem there.
别激动 兄弟
Easy, Lenny.
我想问你考虑过了吗
So, I mean, have you thought about it?
好吧 问题是这样的
Okay, here's the thing.
不 别那么说 我讨厌你那么说
Oh, no. Not "the thing." I hate "the thing."
有什么问题呢
What's "the thing"?
我没办法那么做
I can't do it.
对不起 我真的很想答应
I'm sorry. I wish I could...
听着 你暗恋我
...but, um, see, you have these feelings for me.
等一下 你在担心那个
Wait, wait, wait. That's what you're worried about?
如果那是问题 我们之间没有问题
If that's the problem, we've got no problem.
不 我打算在吃晚餐时告诉你 出差时我认识一个女孩
I was gonna tell you this over dinner, but I met somebody else, on my trip.
她叫作安 她是个记者 我们在飞机上认识
Her name's Ann. She's a journalist. Uh, we met on the plane.
她问我可不可以吃掉我的花生
She asked me if she could finish off my peanuts.
我以为她是指别的东西 我们哈哈大笑
I thought she said something else. We had a big laugh.
我只是厌倦了等待
Yeah, I just... I mean, I got tired of waiting.
那真的很棒 我是说对不起 但我为你感到高兴
Oh, that's great. I mean, I'm sorry, but I'm so happy for you.
- 现在我能为你工作了   - 我想是的
- And now I can work for you.     - I guess you can.
天啊 这太不可思议了
Oh, my God. Oh, this is incredible. Oh.
好吧 你知道吗 我得进办公室提出辞呈
All right. You know what? I'm just gonna roll right into that office and quit.
- 好吧   - 好吧
- All right.     - Okay.
- 你能帮我推一把吗   - 没问题
- Could you give me a little push?     - Yeah, sure.
- 祝你好运   - 我要辞职了
- Good luck.     - I'm quitting. Woo-hoo!
我没事 没问题的
I'm okay. I'm all right.
那真的太棒了 你去了日本 编出一个假女友
Wow. That's exciting. You went to Japan, made up a woman.
什么
What?
我是说这个女人 是你编出来的 对吧
I'm just saying, this woman, I mean, she's fictitious, no?
- 为什么你要那么说   - 因为你还是喜欢摩妮卡
- Why would you say that?     - You're still into Monica.
所以你跟她说你有了别人 她会答应跟你合作
So you told her there's somebody else so she'd agree to work with you.
因为你认为只要有点时间相处 或许她会喜欢上你
Because you figure, if you spend time together, maybe something might happen.
你很厉害 你很厉害
You're good. You're good.
对 不 我的直觉很准 还有通灵能力
Yeah. No, I'm fairly intuitive. And psychic.
那是老天爷的赏赐
It's a substantial gift.
听着 你能答应我不会告诉她吗
Listen, can you promise me that you won't tell her, though?
当然 我保证 跟她说什么
Absolutely. Oh, I promise. Tell her what?
谢谢
Thanks a lot.
不 我是认真的 我的直觉很准 但记忆力超差
No, I'm serious. I mean, I'm intuitive, but my memory sucks.
好吧 这是最后一次
Okay, but this is the last time.
小鸡这边跑跑 那边跑跑
With a chick-chick here And a chick-chick there
这边跑 那边跑  到处跑
Here a chick, there a chick Everywhere a chick-chick
鸡
Chicken
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
她还好吗
How's she doing?
她
She?
对 你不觉得他应该是女的吗
Well, yeah. Don't you think it's a she?
我不知道
I don't know.
我看不出来 不论他是男是女 他的那里很快就缩回去了
I can't tell. Whatever it was, went back in too quickly.
总之我得去换衣服 我要跟一些演员碰面喝酒
Anyway, I gotta change. I'm meeting some of the cast for drinks.
你说什么
Excuse me?
什么
What?
我待在家里 让你去彩排
I stayed home from work while you were at rehearsal...
只为了有人能留在家里照顾小鸡
...so somebody could be here with our chick.
是谁今天凌晨两点到五点没睡
Hey. Who was up from 2:00 this morning until 5:00 this morning...
试着哄他睡觉呢
...trying to get her back to sleep?
你以为你起床时我还在睡吗
You don't think I get up when you get up?
你又来了
Oh, here it comes.
对 我又来了 我整天被关在家里
Yes. Here it comes. I'm stuck here all day.
你一进门 陪了我们两秒钟
And then you come in and spend two seconds with us...
然后你要出门跟朋友花天酒地
...and then expect to go off gallivanting with your friends?
我想那是不对的 先生
Well, I don't think so, mister.
我需要放轻松 好吗 我工作了一整天
Hey. I need to relax, okay? I was working all day.
你不觉得照顾小鸡也是工作
And you don't think taking care of our chick is work?
我不是那个意思 好吧 我是说…
That's not what I said. Okay, I just meant...
我了解你的意思
I know what you meant.
你有发现自从有了小鸡后
Did you notice that ever since we got this chick...
我们吵得比以前厉害吗
...we've been fighting a lot more than we used to?
我不知道 或许我们还没准备好要养小鸡
I don't know, maybe we weren't ready to have a chick.
明天我会送他回去
I'll take her back tomorrow.
你觉得我们能拿回三块钱吗
You think we'll get our 3 bucks back?
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
嘿
Oh. Hey.
听着 两小时后我要录影 我需要你们帮忙
Listen, I have that TV thing in, like, two hours, and I need your help.
好吗 你们觉得如何 蓝色或棕色西装
Okay, what do you think? This blue suit or this brown one?
棕色能衬托你的眼睛
Well, the brown one brings out your eyes.
但你的屁股比较适合穿蓝色的
But your butt looks great in the blue one.
真的吗
Really?
阿斯匹灵舞真的有用
Wow. That aspirin dance really works.
天啊 你还是会…
Oh, my God. Is that still?
我很好
I'm fine. I'm fine.
- 不 才怪   - 我很好
- No, you're not.     - Yes, I am.
- 瑞秋   - 看吧 我很好
- Rach.     - Look, I'm fine.
看吧 看我的
Watch. Look at that. Uh-oh.
好吧 听着 你得去看医生
Okay, okay. Look, you've got to go to a doctor, okay?
不 我得准备到我老板家吃晚餐
No, I have to get ready and go to a dinner at my boss's house.
那很重要 我得跟一些人见面
Very big deal. There's people there that I have to meet.
我相信你会让大家留下深刻印象 "嗨 我是瑞秋•葛林"
Yeah, and I'm sure you're gonna make a great impression. "Hi, I'm Rachel.
"幸会"
It's nice to meet you."
少来了 你可能断了一根肋骨
Come on, you probably have a broken rib.
明天我会去医院 到时候我的肋骨还是断的
Well, I will go to the hospital tomorrow. It'll still be broken then.
但我需要人帮我做准备
But you know, I could use a hand getting ready.
- 瑞秋   - 听着 不帮我就滚出去
- Rachel.     - Look, either help me or go.
好吧 我走就是
Fine. I'll go.
好吧 在你滚出去前 能先帮帮我吗
Okay, but before you go, could you help me first?
好吧 我帮你就是了
Sure. I'll help you.
太好了
Oh, good. Good.
你们知道怎么把小鸡从录影机里拿出来吗
Do you guys know how to get a chick out of a VCR?
你知道吗我没办法用左手这么做
You know what? I cannot do this with my left hand.
你能帮我画眼影吗
Would you please help me with this too?
- 好吧 我们用这支刷子   - 好的
- Okay. Let's use this brush.     - Okay.
- 这个吗 好吧   - 对 小心
- This stuff? All right.     - Yeah. Careful.
轻一点 只要轻轻抹过眼皮
Light. Okay, you know, just sweep it across the lid.
- 好的 抹过去   - 好的
- Okay, just sweep it.     - Okey-dokey.
抱歉
- Oh. Hey.     - Sorry.
- 你戳到我的眼睛   - 抱歉
- Ha, ha. That's poking me in the eye.     - Ha, ha.
抱歉 闭上眼睛
I'm sorry. Close, close, close.
- 抹过去   - 我抹过去了
- Okay, just sweep it.     - I'm sweeping.
- 对   - 抹过去…
- Right.     - Sweep, sweep...
平均一点 因为我不要…
Okay, now make it even, because we don't...
- 什么   - 我不要…
- What?     - We don't want it...
我不想化得太浓 低调一点就好
I don't want it to be too much. I want it to be subtle.
你画再多都不够
You know, you don't wear enough of this.
从什么时候开始你觉得我需要化妆了
Since when...? Since when do you think I don't wear enough of this?
闭上眼睛 我想你会比较喜欢这样 因为…
Well, I... Close your eye. I just think you're gonna like this better because...
- 闭上眼睛   - 吹一下
- Close, close.     - Blow it.
抱歉
Sorry.
因为我觉得这会让你更优雅
Because, um, I think this will make you a little more sophisticated.
跟妓女一样优雅
Sophisticated like a hooker?
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 你猜今晚我要做什么   - 什么
- Guess what I'm doing tonight.     - What?
我要跟彼特去看餐厅
I'm checking out the restaurant with Pete.
- 摩妮卡 我为你感到兴奋   - 我知道
- Oh. Monica, I am so excited for you.     - I know.
我得告诉你一件事
Ooh, I have to tell you something.
- 什么   - 我不能跟你说
- What?     - Well, I can't tell you.
好啊 把不能说的事说出来 应该会比较轻松一点吧
Okay, but wouldn't it be easier to tell me something that you could tell me?
在完美世界里当然是的
Well, sure, in a perfect world.
不 我发誓我不会说的 我跟所有神明发誓过了
But no. I promised I wouldn't tell, and I swore to, like, all my gods.
好吧
Okay.
这跟罗斯及瑞秋有关吗
Does it have to do with Ross and Rachel?
没有
No.
- 跟乔伊有关吗   - 没有
- Does it have to do with Joey?     - No.
这跟钱德及他放在床边的袜子有关吗
Does it have to do with Chandler and that sock that he keeps by his bed?
不 但等一下我们可以谈谈那件事
No, but let's come back to that later.
好了 可以去参加派对了吗
There you go. Good enough for your party? Huh?
当然
Sure.
当然 我可以坐在采购部那个变性人旁边
Sure. I'll just sit next to the transsexual from Purchasing.
得了吧
Come on.
来吧 好了 我该走了 祝你在派对上一切顺利
Okay, come on. All right, I gotta go. So good luck at the party, okay?
等一下 罗斯 你能留下来帮我换衣服吗
Oh, wait, Ross. Could you just stay and help me get dressed?
没问题 好吧
Sure. Okay.
好吧 太棒了 转身
Okay. Okay, great. Um, okay, just turn around.
- 什么   - 我不要你看到我的裸体
- What?     - I don't want you to see me naked.
瑞秋 我看过你的裸体好几百次 我在你的裸体上吃软糖
Rachel, I've seen you naked a million times. I ate hot fudge off you naked.
我从你的肚脐眼吸出迷你棉花糖
I sucked that mini-marshmallow out of your bellybutton.
对 那不一样 当时我们是男女朋友
Yeah, but that was different, you know? We were going out then.
现在感觉怪怪的
Now it's weird.
瑞秋 我随时都能看到你的裸体
Rach, you know, I can see you naked anytime I want.
什么
What?
我只要闭上眼睛 看吧
All I have to do is close my eyes. See? Woo-hoo.
- 罗斯 别那么做   - 对不起
- Ross, stop that.     - I'm sorry.
少来了 我不要你再那样子想我了
Come on. I don't want you thinking of me like that anymore.
抱歉 你一点办法都没有
Uh, sorry. Nothing you can do about it.
那是我身为前男友的特权之一
It's one of my, uh, rights as the ex-boyfriend.
喔 好耶
Huh? Oh. Oh, yeah.
- 住口 别说了   - 好吧
- Stop it. Cut it out. Cut it out.     - Okay, okay.
对不起 我不会再那么做… 哦…
I'm sorry. It will never happen... Uh-oh.
等一下
Wait a minute. Wait, wait...
我看到好几百个你 我是国王
Now there are a hundred of you, and I'm the king.
- 罗斯   - 少来了
- Ross...     - Oh, come on.
你能成熟一点吗 这真的没什么
Would you grow up? It's no big deal.
好吧
All right. Fine.
Okay.
看到你做了什么吗 现在我要自己换衣服
See what you did? I'm gonna be doing it by myself now.
- 好吧 就那样   - 少来了
- Okay, that's it. Ow!     - Oh, come on.
天啊 好吧 听我说
Oh, my God. All right, look, look, okay.
瑞秋 慢慢来 你得去医院
Rach. Easy. Easy. You have to go to the hospital, okay?
- 好吧 我知道了   - 好的
- Okay, I do. I really do.     - Okay.
我帮你拿外套 送你上计程车
Okay, I'm gonna get your coat, then I'll put you in a cab.
等一下 你不陪我去吗
Oh, wait, wait, you're not gonna come with me?
我当然会陪你去
Of course I am.
只是我得去打一通电话
Uh, I just have to make a call.
- 好的   - 好吗
- Okay.     - Okay?
谢谢
Thank you.
怎么了
What's wrong?
抱歉 我不能这样进医院
I'm sorry. I just can't go to the hospital looking like this.
- 跟旅行有关吗   - 没有
- Does it involve travel?     - No.
跟木展有关吗
Does it involve clogs?
等一下 是木展或爪子
Wait, wait. Clogs or claws?
- 木展   - 没有
- Clogs.     - No.
- 爪子   - 没有
- Claws?     - No.
好吧 这跟罗斯 瑞秋 钱德或乔伊无关
Okay, so it doesn't involve Ross or Rachel or Chandler or Joey.
- 彼特呢   - 没有
- What about Pete?     - No.
怎么了
What is it?
- 彼特怎么了   - 我不知道
- What about Pete?     - I don't know.
好吧 我觉得我在跟灵犬莱西说话
Okay, I feel like I'm talking to Lassie.
- 菲比 你能直接告诉我吗   - 不行
- Phoebe, would you just tell me?     - I can't.
- 好吧 我得走了   - 但你只差一点 不要
- Okay, you know, I gotta go.     - But you're so close. No.
跟彼特的电脑公司有关
Something to do with Pete's company?
去吧 你永远都猜不到
Ugh. Just go. You're never gonna get it.
我知道
I know.
看吧 她是亚丝敏•碧莉思
See, yes. That's Yasmine Bleeth.
她是与众不同的美女
She's a completely different kind of chick.
我爱你们两个
I love you both.
但那是不一样的爱
But in very different ways.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
你在做什么 我以为你会送她回去
What are you doing? I though you were gonna take her back.
我有啊 但老板不接受退货
I did. But the store wouldn't take her back.
后来我带她去收容所 你知道我发现了什么吗
So then I took her to the shelter. And you know what I found out?
如果他们无法帮她找到新家 他们会杀了她
If they can't find a home for her, they kill her.
我不能让小亚丝敏有那样的下场
And I'm not gonna let that happen to little Yasmine.
好啊
Okay, good, good, good.
因为我也很犹豫
Because I was kind of having second thoughts too.
好吧 不只是小鸡 所有动物都一样
Okay. And it's not just chicks, you know? It's all kinds of other animals.
那真的很可怕 你这么做是对的
That's horrible. Well, you did the right thing, man.
谢谢 我很高兴你是那么想的
Thanks. I'm glad you see it that way.
喔 这真的非常有趣
Oh, funny story.
我不敢相信
I don't believe this.
看看这个冰箱 真的好大
Wow, look at this refrigerator. It's gigantic.
我可以住在这里 我会着凉 但我一直都很冷
I mean, I could live in this thing. I'd be cold, but I'm always cold.
天啊 看看这些炉子 我超喜欢这些炉子的
Oh, my God. Look at these spider burners. I love spider burners.
你喜欢吗
So you like it?
太完美了 谢谢你
Oh, it is so perfect. Thank you so much.
不客气
You're welcome.
你在闻我的发香吗
Did you just smell my hair?
不 不可能 什么 不
No. No way. What? No.
- 天啊   - 什么
- Oh, God.     - What?
你还是喜欢我 对吧
You still have feelings for me, don't you?
不 我只是为餐厅感到开心
No. I'm just excited about the restaurant, that's all.
- 彼特   - 好吧 我爱你 那很糟糕吗
- Pete?     - Okay, I love you. Is that so bad?
不 那一点都不糟糕
No, it's not bad. It's not bad at all.
这真的很棒
It's really nice.
听着 唯一会受伤害的人是我 我可以接受
Look, the only one who stands to get hurt is me, and I'm okay with that.
对 或许你可以接受被伤害
Yeah, you may be okay with getting hurt...
但我不想当那个伤害你的人
...but I am not okay with being the one who hurts you.
- 所以我无法接受这份工作   - 什么
- That's why I can't take this job.     - What?
或许我们不该再见面了
Well, we probably shouldn't see each other anymore.
对不起
I'm sorry.
好吧
Okay. Yeah.
我是说 如果你真的想这么做 好吧
I mean, if that's really what you want, okay.
好吧 再见
Okay. Bye.
我很遗憾我们无法…
I'm sorry things didn't work out...
暂时闭上你的嘴巴 让我确定一件事
Shut up for a second and let me just see something.
好吧 你没跟我说实话 对吧
Okay, you'd tell me the truth, right?
- 瑞秋 你的X光片看起来不胖   - 好吧
- Rach, you can't look fat in an x-ray.     - Okay.
给我待在那里 好好为你做的事反省一下
Hey, now, you stay out here and you think about what you did.
- 那是一只鸭子   - 那是只坏鸭子
- That's a duck.     - That's a bad duck.
- 今晚你还好吧 罗斯   - 那是…不
- How'd the thing go tonight, Ross?     - Oh, it was... No, no.
什么事
What thing? What thing?
没事 只是博物馆的工作 来吧
Nothing. There was this thing at the museum. Come on.
慢慢走
Easy.
好吧 当你回家后
Okay, now, when you come back...
我希望你记得那只小鸡不是玩具
...I hope you remember that that chick is not a toy.
到底有什么事
What thing? What is this thing?
今晚我原本要上探索频道的节目
Aw, I was kind of supposed to be on TV tonight for the Discovery Channel.
天啊
Oh, my God.
罗斯 为什么你不告诉我
Ross, why didn't you tell me that?
我知道我跟你说的话 你会坚持我一定要去
Ah, I knew that if I told you, you'd make me go...
我知道今晚你需要人陪你 来吧
...and I knew you needed someone to be with you tonight. Come on.
- 来吧   - 我不敢相信你
- Come on.     - I cannot believe you.
- 什么   - 那是最体贴的事
- What?     - That is the sweetest thing.
你该睡一下
You should get some sleep.
好的
Okay.
- 我会…   - 抱歉 我打乱你今晚的计划
- So I'll, um...     - I'm sorry I spoiled your evening.
不 只要你没事就好
No, that's... No, as long as you're okay.
那就…明天见
So I'll, uh... I'll see you tomorrow.
好
Mm-hm. Yeah.
再见
See you.
你做了什么
What did you do?
你在做什么
What you doing?
游泳
Having a swim.
小鸡呢
What about the chick?
小鸡不会游泳
Chicks don't swim.
你确定
Are you sure?
我不知道
I don't know.
- 我们该试试看吗   - 当然
- Should we try?     - Sure.
看吧 我就说他们不会游泳
See, I told you. They don't swim.
- 给他一点时间   - 不
- Well, give him a minute.     - No.
没事的 宝贝
Oh, it's okay. It's okay, baby, baby, baby.